KAMIN GREGOR

1241 Kamnik, Slovenia emeraldDev92@gmail.com

Summary

Highly motivated and Creative Web / Mobile / Blockchain Devloper with deep knowledge in this field. I'd like to build amazing and interesting things that matter. Have years of hands-on experience in building websites and mobile applications using modern Javascript, Typescript, Python, PHP, Ruby frameworks and beautiful UI libraries.

Over the last few years, I mainly focused on Blockchain technologies – build Frontend with Web3 / ether.js / Polkadot / Solidity, Token and Coin.

I Love - Create, Challenge, Collaborate.

EXPERIENCE

04/2013 - 04/2017

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, LIBERTY GLOBAL

- Developed and improved performance of TV setup box software running on Javascript engine Spider Monkey
 - Developed at a TV box weather app
 - Performing well in a remote setting with frequent communication
 - Writing maintainable code that considers accessibility.

04/2017 - 09/2019

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, UPDIVISION

- Build responsive user interfaces with pixel perfect accuracy and fast speed
- Write clean, commented code with React, Vue, Next, Nuxt
- Optimize apps for modularity and speed with various hooks like "useCallback", "useMemo", "dynamic import" and virtualization using React ^16.8
- Always research the best technical solutions and consult with the dev team to implement the best technical solutions

10/2019 - 03/2022

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER, WEBITFACTORY

- Design, build and deploy dApps that run on Ethereum and Solana blockchain using Solidity, Web3, webGL and Moralis
- Build Crypto Data Aggregators for crypto currencies and blockchains with different business objectives
- Build NFT marketplace & P2E games, add token bridge functionality and contributed to Web3 projects
- Lead a team of Frontend, Backend and Smart Contract developers based on the concept of "Let's grow together"

SENIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER, INFRASOFT

- Improved the website's user interface and optimized its speed, resulting in a 35% speed improvement and a 20% increase in user engagement
- Collaborated with the data science team to develop algorithms that matched over 80% of our platform's users with top-performing agents, as a result, 25% increase in customer satisfaction

EDUCATION

TRANSILVANIA UNIVERSITY OF BRASOV, 04/2009-04/2013

BSC, CGPA: 9.20 / 10

Certificate for attending two days workshop on Machine learning

SKILLS

- React
- Vue
- Angular
- Next
- Nuxt
- Django
- Flask
- Laravel
- Elasticsearch
- React kafka
- Blockchain
- Solidity
- Solana
- Rust
- NFT
- NFT marketplace
- ZKP

- Java Spring
- Golang
- Ruby
- Dotnet / Dotnet core
- CI / CD / Git
- Docker
- MySQL
- PostgresSQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- GraphQL
- Hardhat
- Remix
- Polkadot
- Moralis
- Tokenomics
- Metaverse

TYPICAL PROJECTS

- https://www.findlasvegasproperty.com

This is real estate project in Las Vegas. Dev team used modern technologies to improve performance, SEO, functionality.

Used React, Bootstrap, Google Map, Chart.js, kafka, redis, elasticsearch

Had unforgettable experience with so many new tools.

- <u>https://creativ-metalco.ro</u>

This is the site for Metal Fabrications. One of my university friend invites me to this project.

Team finished the project within just 1 month using Laravel.

- https://www.englishhome.com.ro

Our team build this shopping site with Django. As you can see it's so fast.

Used skills: Python, Django

- https://benzi-avertizoare.ro

This is just simple Java Site for Individual Enterprise. Only use Java Spring.

- https://emirateswap.com

This is the prototype big project for team. I've never done such a big project before. What a client want is to extend the functionality of pancakeswap. At first, we were scared to that big project but find a solution to make it easy.

Implemented the prediction with 4 various tokens and lottery with two cryptos.

One of my memorable experience in blockchain field.

Used skill: solidity, hardhat, proxy contract, remix, Business logic

PERSONAL SKILLS AND HOBBIES

- Comprehensive problem solving abilities, taking challenges and learning new skills with confidence
- Ability to deal with people diplomatically
- Reading books and Gardening

TRAINING COURSES

- Linkedin Learning (June 12, 2018)

Master Laravel with Vue.js Full stack development.

Get to know Laravel is the top most PHP framework that provides powerful security Vue + Laravel is the best match, I think. Love this stack.

- Udemy (July 08, 2016)

Full stack React & Redux & Node.js

React changed the way of website development. So redux do. Love MERN, MEAN, MEVN stack.